

Address Raudondvaris, Kauno rajonas

mksolemn@gmail.com

Date of Birth 14.08.1991

PROFILE

I'm full-stack/front-end web developer with over 11 years of experience building web apps. I specialize working with Javascript/Typescript frameworks such as Angular, React, NestJS. I have built and launched successful ecommerce, media, blog websites which receive a huge traffic.

SOFTWARE SKILLS

Javascript	****
HTML,CSS (SASS)	****
Angular	****
NodeJs	****
React	****
AngularJS	****
Bootstrap/Foundation	****
Wordpress	****
Typescript	****
Jquery	****
Chrome extensions	****
Web Scraping(puppeteerJs)	****
MongoDB	****
PHP	****
NestJS	****

PROJECT LINK AND WORK **SAMPLES**

HardHat

https://github.com/mksolemn/cv-workdescription

Mindaugas Kavaliauskas

EDUCATION

2010 - 2014

Kaunas University of Technology, Lithuania Multimedia Engineering

EXPERIENCE

01.2022 - 09.2023

Gamestarter

Full Stack Developer

Building DAPPS for blockchain using NestJS, HardHat & Angular;

Working with StableFusion api to generate images for NFT DAPP;

Building headless Wordpress API, integrated into NestJS proxy API & Angular on front end;

Sample projects: darkfrontiers.com, workstarter.com;

04.2020 - 08.2022

KafeRocks Ltd

Front end Developer

Project description:

Web application designed to help users find relevant casinos for their currently and get best available bonus. Features include: multilingual, responsive design, server side rendering, SEO oriented, best practices. Responsibilities:

Building front end of a gambling operator review blog. Front end stack:

Typescript, React, Gatsby, GraphQL, Webpack, SCSS,

Testing: Jest, Cypress, Sonarqube Code quality: Stylelint, Prettier Cloudflare used for DNS, workers etc...

Live site: https://casinon.info/



LANGUAGES

English
Lithuanian
Russian

PROFILE LINKS

Linkedin: https://goo.gl/gZmF4g Github: https://goo.gl/xZ74AV Behance: Upwork: goo.gl/SdAcLo

SKILLS

Team player
Ability to quickly adapt
Ability to organize own work
Ability to manage time

PERSONALITY

Eager to learn
Punctual
Professional
Organized

HOBBIES

Programming, Technology, Gaming, Calisthenics, Movies...

04.2017 - 04.2020

StreamAMG

Senior Front end Developer

As front-end developer for StreamAMG I build video streaming web applications in scalable and collaborative way - focusing on creating fast and responsive UI/UX while emphasizing code structure and component modularity and ease of use. Aside from web applications, largest product that I contributed to was Kaltura video player. My responsibilities for video player development included: different ad providers integration, payment system integration for paid content, UI/UX....

Latest noteworthy projects:
https://www.livebasketball.tv/home
https://video.avfc.co.uk/home?lang=en
https://video.leedsunited.com/home
https://video.asroma.com/on-demand?lang=en
https://video.pdc.tv/?lang=en
Technical stack: Angular, SASS, Nodejs, PHP, Wordpress,
Kaltura video Platform.

09.2016 - 01.2017

Media Plan

Web developer

Building wordpress sites, creating custom plugins.
Building widgets and banners, for marketing, using
front end technologies. Creating custom chrome plugins
to automate marketing. Web scraping with node.js,
nightmare.js, casper.js, phantom.js

03.2016 - 07.2016

Platin Gaming Ltd.

Front end developer

Building front end for game management applications: Online application for horse and dog betting; Slicing PSD design into HTML; Affiliate marketing – creating and managing wordpress pages.

03.2015 - 01.2016

Sekasoft

AngularJS developer

Build and design AngularJS SPA for sharepoint. App functions: sort, filter and paginate employee list.

08.2014 - present

Freelance front end, shopify developer

Creating designs and themes for ecommerce stores